Hemangi Sangole

Software Tester

8329761755

sangolehemangi@gmail.com

Nashik, Maharashtra, 422006, India

https://www.linkedin.com/in/hemangi-s-58488b250

As a software testing professional having experience in writing test scripts, debugging and review software at each stage of development and production. Collaborates with the software team in continuous build and deployment process. Worked on projects spanning a diverse area. Proficient user of the AI tools for better efficiency. Curious to learn new software tools and best practices in software QA.

Experience

Software Tester, ESDS Software Solutions Pvt Ltd, Nashik

Aug 2022 - July 2024

Responsible for functional and non-functional testing for ERP system implemented by using SSO. Executing Test Cases and generating Test summary Reports. Log defect in JIRA. Writing and executing tests-scripts for Load testing using Jmeter. Android Mobile app testing. Power Bi reports testing. Automation of the Portals of the ERP system.

Manual and Automation Tester, NexTech Services Pvt Ltd, Pune

Dec 2018 - Aug 2022

Responsible for writing and maintaining Selenium Web Driver scripts for regression and functional testing using Data Driven Framework. Developed test code in Java language using Eclipse, IDE and TestNG framework. Identified, Reported and Tracked Defects using JIRA test management tool.

Education

July 2010 - Sept 2014

Masters of Engg (Electronics), MGM's JNEC, Aurangabad (BAMU)

July 2003 - Sept 2008

Bachelors of Engg (Electronics and Telecomm), PREC, Loni (SPPU)

Skills

Manual TestingFunctional TestingTest Case DesignTest PlanningSDLC and STLCAgile MethodologyAPI Testing (POSTMAN)Android Mobile App TestingLoad Testing (Jmeter)Automation TestingSelenium WebdriverTestNGJIRAGithubJAVA using Eclipse

Python

Jenkins BDD Cucumber

Certificates

ISTQB CTFL Certified - 13/08/2024

JIRA Fundamentals Badge - 03/11/2023

Basic Reporting in Jira Badge - 18/10/2023

Agile with Atlassian JIRA – 04/10/2023

Certified Entry-Level Python Programmer - 05/01/2021

Projects Promoted

Project Costing proposed for the CMMI level 5.